The trial of the Celestial Realm
is supposed to be about seeking the Dao.
But because of a century-old grudge,
a manhunt
across star systems took place.
The Blood Ancestor crossed star systems
and came to the Thunder Celestial Realm.
A mighty being's rage
spilled endless blood.
In the depths of despair,
Wang Lin received help from his friend Li Yuan
and by borrowing the laws of the heavens and the earth,
he fought the Blood Ancestor to the death.
It was a certain death battle
but he ended up slaying the Immortal against all odds.
Renegade Immortal Movie\N\NBattle of the Immortal Slayer
Stay tuned
The rules keep changing.
I've been rehearsing every possible outcome.
Once this thought arises, there is no more room for right or wrong.
I am resolved to sever this flood
so that my soul can break free from mediocrity,
from loneliness and distinction.
One more step and you'll fall into madness.
Don't fall down.
I look towards the top.
Chase !
Refined to perfection.
Never retreat, no matter the danger.
I dare to defy the heavens !
Always overcome the obstacles,
ignite the seas with blood,
bloom through trials and tribulations.
Even the sharpest thorns
will be reduced into ashes.
What is there to fear ?
Renegade Immortal\NSubtitles by Bonobosubs\Nhttps://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
1 year later
Void between Thunder\NCelestial Realm fragments
Yan Chou\NGuard of the Yao Family\NIllusory Yin
Ru Yun\NYao Lao's cousin\NEarly stage Ascendant
Yao Luo\NYao Family's branch member\NPeak Late stage Ascendant
He lasted 13 days.
Better than the ones before him.
Young Master,
this guy is already at his last breath.
Uncle Chou,
it looks like we need to catch an Illusory Yin cultivator next time
so I can play a few more days.
Alright.
Cousin,
this guy still has a few swords on him.
I won't forget.
They're all yours.
Not to mention these 9 swords,
everything in this Thunder Celestial Realm
can become mine
if I wish.
Cousin, you're from the Yao Family,
of course you can get anything you want.
I can't hold on any longer...
If you want my artifacts, take them.
Why would you humiliate me to this extent ?
Even if I become a ghost,
I will never let you off !
You're overestimating yourself.
A member of the Li Family,
even in death...
will keep its dignity !
Break.
Annihilation
Restriction Heart !
Now die !
Brother Xu...
I won't be able to give you
my Restriction Heart anymore.
Let me see
where exactly
you got those 9 celestial swords.
Cousin,
hurry up.
Young Master, retreat !
Who gave you the qualifications
to hurt my friend ?
Spatial Bending !?
I know all the Corporeal Yang cultivators who entered the Thunder Celestial Realm,
but who is he !?
Brother Xu...
Help me
to kill them.
Wang Lin's avatar\NCorporeal Yang
If he has such a powerful friend,
why didn't he say so earlier !?
How long did you chase my friend ?
Senior, let me speak !
It was the Yao Young Master...
How long !?
Thir...
Thirteen days...
Stop !
This is for the first day.
The second day !
The third day !
Stop !
The fourth day !
Fifth...
Sixth...
Seventh !
Thirteenth !
Junior,
you killed a member of the Yao Family.
The Yao Family will exterminate your entire family !
Do you recognize him ?
The aura of the Yao Family's direct bloodline ?
You...!
Brother Li,
I will give you an opportunity.
Whether you can reach Illusory Yin
depends on your luck.
Cave Residence\NThunder Celestial Realm
Li Yuan has been stuck at Peak Ascendant for years
not because he lacks talent
but because he lacked origin energy.
By infusing him with origin energy today,
he may be able to breakthrough.
In such a short time,
I was hunted by an all-powerful Nirvana Cleanser.
Had I chosen to flee and avoid the fight that day,
I would have likely become a blood slave
or have died with my Dao exterminated.
To slay this Immortal,
I had to narrowly escape death
and I obtained this Corporeal Yang cultivation.
A defensive formation of this scale
isn't something I could've done before.
The Corporeal Yang realm
is not only a higher cultivation level
but it also grants a higher mastery over the laws of the world.
Refining an entire Celestial Realm fragment into an artifact
really made this trip worthwile.
Thunder Celestial Realm\NFragment Stamp
Wan'er...
Wait for me.
I will definitely go to Planet Dong Lin.
Even if there is only a sliver of a chance to awaken you,
I will not let it go.
Before going to Dong Lin,
I still need to master more celestial spells and artifacts.
This object is formed from half of the Blood Ancestor's blood body,
it's very powerful.
If I refine it a bit,
it may save my life
at a critical moment.
This artifact isn't ordinary.
I have tried several times
but I can't imprint my Divine Sense on it.
Could there be another secret to it ?
When I obtained this bone,
it was with these celestial swords.
As expected !
The celestial swords and the beast bone
are able to make a faintly perceptible formation.
If not for this nested formation,
my Divine Sense would have no way in.
A restriction world was hidden in the sword ?
This restriction is brilliant,
it's unlike anything I've ever seen.
The one who set it is no ordinary Celestial.
To claim this artifact,
I must find the formation's eye
to break the restriction.
I found it !
All these restrictions
are chained together
in a restriction matrix.
To imprint my Divine Sense,
I need to
break all the restrictions at once !
Fall !
Withered Dao Pair
According to the memory of the previous Divine Sense imprint,
this thing
is called the Withered Dao Pair.
It's a true celestial artifact.
It was damaged in the war against the Ancient Gods.
After its master died,
it wasn't fully repaired.
Even in its damaged state,
its power is still astonishing.
It's one of my most powerful artifacts right now.
Yao
Yao Family of Allheaven...
Ever since I killed the Blood Ancestor,
a blood feud was created.
Another talisman ?
This talisman
is extremely similar to the one I obtained from Xu Fenghan.
Note: Xu Fengshan, Illusory Yin from Planet Dong Lin (episode 149)
Origin energy fluctuations !
If not for my improved cultivation,
I wouldn't have detected it.
This should be a special artifact
but I don't know how to use it for now.
Collection Pavilion...
So this Illusory Yin Elder entered the Thunder Celestial Realm
to escort a member of the Yao Family to this pavilion
to obtain celestial spells.
This pavilion was personally built by the Thunder Celestial Emperor
and stores countless celestial spells.
Now, the four great ancient families with a Celestial bloodline
have joined forces to seal this place
and only allow those with a Celestial bloodline to enter
in search of opportunities.
The Yao Family
is one of them.
Brother Xu,
thank you.
But my Origin Soul can't withstand that much origin energy.
It seems that
I'm not fated to reach Illusory Yin.
Brother Li, don't underestimate yourself.
The origin energy within you will keep nourishing your Origin Soul.
When it's fully absorbed,
you will reach Illusory Yin.
That day
may come sooner or later.
Success lies in perseverance.
I'm returning what belongs to you.
Keep them safe.
These artifacts and celestial jades
will also help your cultivation.
This is a Restriction-Breaking Ancient Mirror,
Restriction-Breaking\NAncient Mirror
there are very few of these left.
If you ever need to break a restriction quickly,
it may be of help to you.
I can no longer see through
Brother Xu's cultivation.
As for slaying that Immortal...
It was only possible thanks to Brother Li's restrictions.
Although the Blood Ancestor isn't dead yet,
he no longer poses a threat.
Brother Li,
I wish to go to a place called the Collection Pavilion
to obtain celestial spells.
But this place is sealed by restrictions.
Brother Li is far more familiar with the Thunder Celestial Realm than I am.
Do you want to come with me ?
I will follow Brother Xu
wherever you go.
Celestial Guiding Palace\NThunder Celestial Realm
Brother Xu,
The Collection Pavilion is to the southwest
and there are several ancient Celestial ruins nearby.
Do you want to explore them too ?
If Brother Li thinks they're worth visiting,
then the more opportunities,
the better.
This rundown place
Celestial Welcoming\NPalace
has probably been cleaned up already.
What's there to look around for ?
This Celestial Welcoming Palace
seems to be a place where ancient Celestials traded.
Brother Xu's guess is right.
According to ancient records,
in these kinds of Celestial markets,
the largest shop is always to the east.
My Divine Sense found nothing unusual.
See ?
Not even a single hair left.
Brother Xu,
please strike this spot with full force.
There really was a hidden formation.
It's a pity this formation is too old,
its celestial spiritual energy is gone,
it's a dead formation.
Not bad.
But my Li Family's restrictions
can restore this dead formation.
Li Yuan really is
a restriction prodigy.
If he were with me in the Rain Celestial Realm,
maybe he could have reverse-engineered
the illusory palm strike.
I did it !
The spirit of the formation ?
This is the first time this formation has been opened !
Once this beam of light disperses,
we will be able to enter.
This formation is making too much of a commotion,
I'm afraid it will attract unwanted attention.
A heavenly phenomenon !
A treasure must have appeared !
Quick !
Those who enter
will die !
The two of us are Juniors from the Zhao Family of the Western Domain.
We respectfully obey Senior's order.
We would never dare to offend you.
30 minutes later
What's the situation down there ?
Do you know ?
It seems there are only two people.
That Senior is clearly a second step cultivator.
Why don't you step in there yourself ?
Fellow cultivator, wait !
Tang Yanyun\NTang Family member\NIllusory Yin
The Tang Family !
One of the strongest in the Southern Domain.
No wonder they are so high-profile.
Brother Li can enter first.
Leave this person to me.
Alright.
I am Tang Yanyun.
My Tang Family
would like to invite fellow cultivator to explore this cave together.
What do you think ?
You are not qualified.
I'm sorry for disturbing you.
You won't give my Tang Family some face ?
A mere rogue cultivator...
Once my Senior Brother arrives,
he will easily take down this guy.
My thunder is not something
you're qualified to devour either !
You dare !
An ignorant nobody
dares to act so arrogantly in front of the Tang Family !?
You must pay the price !
I said that
those who enter
will die.
What artifact is this ?
I...
I'm from the Tang Family !
You can't kill me !
Kill him
and I'll bury you with him.
Senior Brother,
save me quickly !
You dare to kill a member of the Tang Family before the Young Master ?
Tang Ping\NTang Family member\NIllusory Yin
You must be tired of living.
In this 10 000 zhang area,
those who enter will die.
What a joke !
There is actually someone
in the Thunder Celestial Realm
who dares to proclaim a forbidden area !
This guy...
How can he have such killing intent ?
Could he...
be cultivating the Dao of Slaughter !?
Dao...
This is his Dao !
I'll give you his corpse back intact.
Fellow cultivator,
please tell us your name.
Xu Mu
Ask
Qi Condensation
the perilous path filled with countless blades.
Foundation Establishment
Can the mundane world be shattered
Core Formation
Nascent Soul
by a child's steadfast heart ?
If the laws of this world
Soul Formation
Soul Transformation
stand in the way,
I'll defy the universe to tread the heavens
Ascendant
and ask this question to the sky.
My heart's deepest wish
is to not kneel before these mountains and rivers.
Don't accept your doomed fate,
karma can be changed.
Unwilling to let go,
my obsessions propel me forward.
Don't be afraid.
Thunder rumbles as I dare to tread through the reincarnation cycle.
Accept your fate and stay mortal or defy it to become immortal.
Hold fast to this resolve and break through the obstacles.
I'll fight all those who dare to stand in my way.
Let the winds of war heed my command.
I sign this question with my heart.
What is the Dao ?
Defying the flow of heaven and earth,
the heart I cultivate stays true.
I contemplate the wisdom of heaven and earth.
I shall choose my path between karma and fate.
My unshakable Dao Heart
aspires to ascend.
Defying,
this is what my journey to treading the heavens relies on.
Accept your fate and stay mortal or defy it to become immortal.
Hold fast to this resolve and break through the obstacles.
I'll fight all those who dare to stand in my way.
Let the winds of war heed my command.
I sign this question with my heart.
What is the Dao ?
Defying the flow of heaven and earth,
the heart I cultivate stays true.
I contemplate the wisdom of heaven and earth.
I shall choose my path between karma and fate.
My unshakable Dao Heart
aspires to ascend.
Defying,
this is what my journey to treading the heavens relies on.